Guide to the Pittsburgh Regional Library Center Records, 1967-1985 AIS.1990.12
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Pittsburgh Regional Library Center Records
1967-1985
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Pittsburgh Regional Library Center
AIS.1990.12
12.5 Linear Feet (10 boxes)
This collection contains records of the Pittsburgh Regional Library Center, including minutes of the board of trustees, the executive council, and several committees, budgets, directories, state contracts, grants, activities files, and booklets.
History
The Pittsburgh Regional Library Center (PRLC) was incorporated in 1967 for the purpose of facilitating resource sharing among academic, public, and school libraries. According to PRLC's by-laws, the center was "formed for the charitable, scientific, literary and educational purposes of advancing library science, for the promotion of library services, and for the promotion of inter-library cooperation among the public and private libraries in the City of Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, and surrounding areas to a distance of 200 miles."
Initial funding for the Center was provided by the A. W. Mellon Educational and Charitable Trust. A local clearinghouse was established in the early 1970s with funds from the Hillman Foundation. The PRLC was governed by a fifteen-member Board of Trustees. Twelve members of the board were elected from the membership and the other three came from the community-at-large. The Executive Director served ex-officio.
On November 30, 1995 the PRLC officially merged with Palinet assuming all assets and liabilities. The Palinet headquarters remained in Philadelphia, and eventually merged with SOLINET and NELINET to form LYRASIS in 2009.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains records of the Pittsburgh Regional Library Center, including minutes of the board of trustees, the executive council, and several committees, budgets, directories, state contracts, grants, activities files, and booklets.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Deposited by Pittsburgh Regional Library Center in 1990.
Previous Citation
Pittsburgh Regional Library Center Records, 1967-1985, AIS.1990.12, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Libraries -- Pennsylvania; Library cooperation -- Pennsylvania; Associations; Pittsburgh Regional Library Center
- Advisory Panel on Union List, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Advisory Panel on Union List Subcommittee, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A/V Instructional Materials for Reference use (Ad Hoc Committee), 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A/V Instructional Materials for Reference use (Ad Hoc Committee), 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A/V Instructional (Ad Hoc Committee), 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- A/V Instructional Materials Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1979-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- A/V Instructional Materials Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- A/V Instructional Materials Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- A/V Instructional Materials Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- A/V Instructional Materials Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- A/V Instructional Materials Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- A/V - New York Times Index (Box 1, Folder 12)
- A/V Workshops held at Robert Morris University, May 3 and 11, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Audit, Budget Finance (Standing Committee), 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Audit, Budget Finance (Standing Committee), 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Audit, Budget Finance (Standing Committee), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Audit, Budget Finance (Standing Committee), 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Audit, Budget Finance (Standing Committee), 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Audit, Budget Finance (Standing Committee), 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Audit, Budget Finance (Standing Committee), 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Automation Discussion Committee (not an ad hoc committee), IV.
- Automation Discussion Committee (not an ad hoc committee), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Automation Discussion Committee (not an ad hoc committee), 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Automation Discussion Committee (not an ad hoc committee), 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Automation Discussion Committee (not an ad hoc committee), 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Background Materials (Box 1, Folder 25)
- By-Laws Revision, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- By-Laws Revision, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Board of Trustees, VI.
- Board of Trustees Meetings, February 26, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, May 21, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, September 24, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, February 25, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, April 13, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, May 24, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, September 29, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, February 16, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, May 18, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, October 5, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, February 11, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, May 17, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, September 23, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, January 29, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, May 16, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, September 19, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Board of Trustees Special Meetings, January 16, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, May 21, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, September 17, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, January 21, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, May 16-17, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, September 16, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, February 24, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, May 19, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, September 15, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, February 16, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, May 18, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, September 21, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, January 18, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, May 23, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, September 19, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, January 23, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, May 15, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, September 25, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, January 15, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, May 21, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, September 17, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, January 28, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, May 20, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Board of Trustees Regular Meetings, September 16, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Budget/Finance (Standing Committee), 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Budget/Finance (Standing Committee), 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Preliminary Budget (Proposed F76-77), 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Budget Proposals, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Budget Proposals, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Cataloging Subcommittee, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Cataloging Subcommittee, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Cataloging Subcommittee, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Cataloging Subcommittee, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Clearinghouse (general), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Clearinghouse for Interlibrary Loan (Ad Hoc Committee), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Clearinghouse for Interlibrary Loan (Ad Hoc Committee), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
- Clearinghouse for Interlibrary Loan (Ad Hoc Committee), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
- Clearinghouse for Interlibrary Loan (Ad Hoc Committee), 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Clearinghouse for Interlibrary Loan (Ad Hoc Committee), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Clearinghouse, Misc., 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Clearinghouse Committee, (PRLC), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Clearinghouse Committee, (PRLC), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
- Clearinghouse Committee, (PRLC), 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
- Clearinghouse Committee, (PRLC), 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
- Clearinghouse Committee, (PRLC), 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Committee Guidelines - ILL info. (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Clearinghouse, Intern, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Clearinghouse, Intern, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Clearinghouse, Microfilming, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Clearinghouse, Non-member Services, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Clearinghouse, Non-member Services, Invoices Calendar, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Clearinghouses in Pa. (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Committees (general info.), 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Computer Applications Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Conservation Preservation Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Conservation Preservation Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Conservation Preservation Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Conservation Preservation Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Conservation Preservation Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Cooperative Acquisitions Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Cooperative Acquisitions Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Cooperative Binding (Ad Hoc), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Cooperative Purchasing, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Cooperative Purchasing, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Database Services Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Database Services Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Database Services Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Database Services Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Database Services Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Database Services Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Database Services Committee (Ad Hoc Committee), 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- PRLC - Delphi Study (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Energy Information Center (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Ethnic Collections (Ad Hoc Committee), 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Ethnic Collections (Ad Hoc Committee), 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Ethnic Collections (Ad Hoc Committee), 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Ethnic Collections (Ad Hoc Committee), 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Executive Council, general, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Executive Council, general, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Executive Council, general, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Executive Council, general, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Executive Council, general, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Executive Council Meeting, July 23, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Executive Council Meeting, September 9, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Executive Council Meeting, October 8, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Executive Council Meeting, November 5, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Executive Council Meeting, December 3, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Executive Council Meeting, January 7, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Executive Council Meeting, January 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Executive Council Meeting, February 25, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Executive Council Meeting, March 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Executive Council Meeting, March 10, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Executive Council Meeting, March 31, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Executive Council Meeting, April 13, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Executive Council Meeting, April 28, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Executive Council Meeting, May 21, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Executive Council Meeting, June 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Executive Council Meeting, July 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Executive Council Meeting, August 9, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Executive Council Meeting, September 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Executive Council Meeting, October 19, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Executive Council Meeting, November 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Executive Council Meeting, December 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Executive Council Meeting, January 4, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Executive Council Meeting, January 19, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Executive Council Meeting, February 16, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Executive Council Meeting, March 16, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Executive Council Meeting, April 12, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Executive Council Meeting, June 15, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Executive Council Meeting, July 27, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Executive Council Meeting, September 14, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Executive Council Meeting, October 26, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Executive Council Meeting, November 21, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Executive Council Meeting, December 21, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Executive Council Meeting, February 6, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Executive Council Meeting, March 22, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Executive Council Meeting, April 19, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Executive Council Meeting, May 17, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Executive Council Meeting, June 14, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Executive Council Meeting, June 13, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Executive Council Meeting, September 7, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Executive Council Meeting, October 11, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Executive Council Meeting, November 16, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Executive Council Meeting, December 13, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Executive Council Meeting, January 10, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Executive Council Meeting, January 29, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Executive Council Meeting, February 14, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Executive Council Meeting, March 14, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Executive Council Meeting, April 16, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Executive Council Meeting, May 9, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Executive Council Meeting, June 13, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Executive Council Meeting, August 15, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Executive Council Meeting, September 19, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Executive Council Meeting, October 17, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Executive Council Meeting, November 14, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Executive Council Meeting, December 12, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Executive Council Meeting, January 15, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Executive Council Meeting, February 20, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Executive Council Meeting, March 19, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Executive Council Meeting, April 16, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Executive Council Meeting, May 18, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Executive Council Meeting, June 18, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Executive Council Meeting, July 11-12, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  General note
  Mailing only.
- Executive Council Meeting, August 1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Executive Council Meeting, September 19, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Executive Council Meeting, October 29, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Executive Council Meeting, November 24, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Executive Council Meeting, December 17, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Executive Council Meeting, January 21, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Executive Council Meeting, February 18, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Executive Council Meeting, March 18, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Executive Council Meeting, April 23, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Executive Council Meeting, May 13, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Executive Council Meeting, June 17, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Executive Council Meeting, August 19, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Executive Council Meeting, September 17, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Executive Council Meeting, October 15, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Executive Council Meeting, November 18, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Executive Council Meeting, December 16, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Executive Council Meeting, January 13, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Executive Council Meeting, February 17, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Executive Council Meeting, March 17, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Executive Council Meeting, April 21, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Executive Council Meeting, May 19, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Executive Council Meeting, June 16, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Executive Council Meeting, July 1982 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  No meeting.
- Executive Council Meeting, September 3, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Executive Council Meeting, October 12, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Executive Council Meeting, November 12, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Executive Council Meeting, December 12, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Executive Council Meeting, January 26, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Executive Council Meeting, February 18, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Executive Council Meeting, March 18, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Executive Council Meeting, April 22, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Executive Council Meeting, May 18, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Executive Council Meeting, June 17, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Executive Council Meeting, August 3, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Executive Council Meeting, September 7, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Executive Council Meeting, October 21, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Executive Council Meeting, November 30, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Executive Council Meeting, December 19, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Executive Council Minutes, January 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Executive Council Minutes, February 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Executive Council Minutes, March 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Executive Council Minutes, April 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Executive Council Minutes, May 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Executive Council Minutes, June 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Expensive Items List, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Expensive Items List, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Forty Month PRLC Plan, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Goals/Structure/Means, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Goals/Structure/Means, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Government Document Workshop, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Grants (old), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Headquarters office meetings visits, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Hillman Foundation Grant for Clearinghouse (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Hillman Grant -- Pilot Project to max periodicals, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
- Interlibrary Lending code (PRLC) (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Interlibrary Loan Policy, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- LSCA Grant- Union List of Periodicals, March-December 1970 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- LSCA Grant- Union List of Serials, January 2, 1972-June 30, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- LSCA Grant- Union List of Serials, February 15, 1973-June 30, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- LSCA Grant- FFY, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- LSCA Grant- FFY, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- LSCA Title III- Grant for 25,000 for Microfilming card cat. (Box 6, Folder 25)
- LSCA Title III- Transitional funds, OCLC participants (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Major Micro - correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Marketing committee, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Membership Assessments, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Membership Assessments, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Membership Assessments, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Membership Assessments, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Membership, Standing Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Membership, Standing Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Membership, Public Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Membership, Public Relations, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- (PRLC) Metropolitan Science Technology Lib. (MSTL) (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Needs Assessment, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Negotiating Committee -- OCLC Serials Data Base, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Newspaper Directory, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Newspaper Directory, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Newspaper Directory, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Newspaper Indexing Project, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Newspaper List (order, invoices)(PRLC) (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Newspaper List Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Newspaper List Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Newspaper List Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Nominating Committee, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Nominating Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Nominating Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Nominating Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Nominating Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Nominating Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Nominating Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Nominating Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Nominating Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Nominating Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- OCLC Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- OCLC Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- OCLC Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- OCLC Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- OCLC Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- OCLC Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- OCLC Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- OCLC Committee, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- OCLC Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Online cataloging, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Online cataloging, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Online cataloging, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Online cataloging, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Original Proposal to State Library of Pennsylvania for OCLC (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Online Services Committee, 1983-84 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Online Union List of Periodicals, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
- Operations- Standing Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Operations- General, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
- Operations- Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Operations- General, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 18-19)
- Operations- General, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
- Operations- General, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Operations- General, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
- Operations- General, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 25-26)
- Pennyslvania State Advisory Committee, 1981-82 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Pennsylvania Periodicals Pilot for Access Locations (Pa. Per PAL) (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Peer Council Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Peer Council Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Peer Council Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Peer Council Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Peer Council Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Peer Council Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Personnel Policies Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Personnel Policies Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- PRLC Membership, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- PRLC Membership, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- PRLC Membership, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- PRLC Membership, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- PRLC Membership, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- PRLC conference, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- PRLC Membership Directory, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Program Services, Conference on government documents (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Program Services, Conferences Seminars Hillman automation (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Program Services, "Expensive Items" (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Program Services, "On order" periodicals file (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Program Services, Undergraduate Inter Lib. Borrowing (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Proposals Grant applications, HEA title IIA, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Proposals Grant applications, Interlibrary Cooperation Questionnaire (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Proposals Grant applications, Union Catalog for art holdings (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Proposals and Studies- Cooperation Conservation Program (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Proposals and Studies- PRLC Handbook (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Proposals -Automated cataloging system for PRLC, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Reasons for joining PRLC - summary, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)